elevenwireless.com 2003-06-03

# eleven wireless : instant wireless internet access

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

  * This policy covers how **eleven wireless** treats personal information that it collects and receives. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, and/or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that **eleven wireless** does not own or control, or to people that **eleven wireless** does not employ or closely manage.

**Information Collection and Use**   
**General**

  * **eleven wireless** collects personal information when you register with **eleven wireless** , when you use **eleven wireless** products or services, when you visit **eleven wireless** pages or the pages of certain **eleven wireless** partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. **eleven wireless** may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. If we offer financial products and services, we may also ask for your address, Social Security number, and information about your assets. Once you register with **eleven wireless** and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * **eleven wireless** collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we could offer. 
  * **eleven wireless** automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, MAC address, **eleven wireless** cookie information, and the page you request. 
  * **eleven wireless** may use information it collects for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

**Children**   
This Web site is not to be used by any child under age 13. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * **eleven wireless** does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 
    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with **eleven wireless** under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help **eleven wireless** communicate with you about offers from **eleven wireless** and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of **eleven wireless** 's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
    * We transfer information about you if **eleven wireless** is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, **eleven wireless** will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 
  * **eleven wireless** may display targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. 
    * **eleven wireless** does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 
    * **eleven wireless** advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies). 

**Cookies**

  * **eleven wireless** may set and access **eleven wireless** cookies on your computer. 
  * **eleven wireless** may let other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to **eleven wireless** 's cookies. 
  * **eleven wireless** may use web beacons to access **eleven wireless** cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with **eleven wireless** products and services. 

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**   
**General**

  * You can edit your **eleven wireless** account information, including your marketing preferences, at any time by contacting **eleven wireless**. 
  * Users who contact **eleven wireless** can opt out of receiving future marketing communications or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive. 
  * Certain communications from **eleven wireless** , such as service announcements, administrative messages and the **eleven wireless** Newsletter, are considered part of **eleven wireless** membership and you may not opt out of receiving them. 
  * You can delete your **eleven wireless** account by contacting **eleven wireless**. Confidentiality and Security 
  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you. 
  * Your **eleven wireless** Account Information is password-protected. 
  * In certain areas **eleven wireless** uses industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

**eleven wireless** may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your **eleven wireless** account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**Questions and Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions, please complete a feedback form or you can contact us at: 

****eleven wireless**** inc.   
Customer Care - Privacy Policy Issues   
1631 NW Thurman   
Portland, OR 97209   
(503) 222-4321
